## Contact

- Mizmizi East Painadi, Siddhirganj 1430
- 01991896271
- rakibulhassanovi123@gm ail.com

### Skills

Flutter

Very Good

Dart



Microsoft Office



English





My name is Rakibull Hasan Ovi. I am a frontend Flutter developer. I did 04 months internship in a company. Its name is Popcorn IT. It is located at Nikonjo 2, Khilkhet. I can develop any UI/UX design. I completed Diploma Engineering in CSE from Dhaka Polytechnic Institute. I am a friendly, kind and polite person and also a good learner. I can do anything if it is necessary for me. Now need real life experience so I can develop my skills. I can learn very fast. Hope you will not be disappointed with my series.

Here is my GitHub link :- https://github.com/RakibullHasanOvi Here is my WhatsApp number :- 01991896271

# Work History

2022-10 - **Frontend App Developer** 2023-01 POPCORN IT, Nikonjo 2, Khilkhet

### Education

2016-01 - S.S.C (Secondary School Certificate): Science

Siddhirganj Reboti Mohan Pilot School & College

- Siddhirganj Bazar, Siddhirgan-1430,

Narayanganj

2018-08 - **Diploma Engineering: Computer** 

2023-03 Science And Engineering

Dhaka Polytechnic Institute - Tejgaon, Dhaka,

Bangladesh

### Certifications

2018-02 Secondary School Certificate GPA - 4.61

2023-05 Diploma Engineering CGPA - 3.56